Preliminary Inventory for the American Guild of Variety Artists Records WAG.095
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VIII: Financial Records, Welfare Fund Minutes
  - Financial Reports; USO Camp Shows, Inc.; Coscia, Philadelphia office files, 1955-1966 (Box 156)
  - Welfare Trust Fund, including correspondence, financial records, 1971-1974 (Box 157)
  - Welfare Trusts Fund, 1975-1977 (Box 158)
- Series IX: Miscellaneous
  Series IX: Miscellaneous, 1949-1981, 4 linear feet. Includes microfilm minutes of the National Conventions and Board meetings, photographs, ephemera, sample contracts and other miscellaneous material.
  - Microfilm-National Conventions and Board meetings: photographs, ephemera, 1940s-1950s (Box 159)
  - Standard contract forms, correspondence with producing organizations, minimum basic agreements, 1962-1981 (Box 160)
  - Miscellaneous microfilm and other misc., 1952-1980 (Box 161)
- Series X: Archived Website, Apr 23, 2012-ongoing
  The American Guild of Variety Artists (AGVA) is an AFL-CIO-affiliated labor union founded in 1939 to represent performing artists and stage managers for live performances in the variety field. The variety area of performance includes singers and dancers in touring shows and in theatrical revues, theme park performers, skaters, circus performers, comedians & stand-up comics, cabaret & club artists, lecturers, poets, monologists, spokespersons, and variety performers working at private parties special events. AGVA is a branch of The Associated Actors and Artistes of America. AGVA negotiates contracts and provides relief for members. The website contains information on their relief funds, auditions, news, and other information.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.